t3leads.com 2019-03-20

# T3leads Privacy Policy

**Last Updated: October 18, 2016**

Thank you for visiting the T3Leads website located at www.t3leads.com (the "Site"). The Site is an Internet property of D and D Marketing, Inc. ("T3Leads," "we" or "us"). T3Leads is committed to protecting the privacy of our visitors` personally identifiable information. We provide this privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") in order to explain our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is used by us. This Privacy Policy applies to any and all information submitted or collected on this Site. You agree to this Privacy Policy, in its entirety, when you: (a) access or use our Site; and/or (b) register on the Site to participate in the T3Leads Network ("Network") as an Advertiser and/or Affiliate. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy in its entirety, you are not authorized to become an Affiliate or Advertiser ("Network Member") and/or use the Site in any manner or form whatsoever.

## Personally Identifiable Information

Some of the information you must provide to register as a Network Member or otherwise choose to provide to T3Leads is Personally Identifiable Information. Personally Identifiable Information is unique data about an individual used for identification and communication purposes. Personally Identifiable Information may include—without limitation—name, birth date, home and/or mobile telephone numbers, personal email address, and mailing and/or home address.

## Non-Personally Identifiable Information

Some information you must provide, or which may be collected by virtue of your access to and/or use of this Site, may include non-Personally Identifiable Information. Non-Personally Identifiable Information may include—without limitation—Internet Protocol address, browser type, operating system type, and Internet Service Provider.

## Cookies

This Site employs the use of Cookies to enhance your user experience. Cookies are data sent to your computer when you visit a website. Cookies allow this Site to recognize your browser and store your preferences. Cookies help T3Leads analyze traffic on this Site to better understand visitor behavior and other activity. Cookies, by themselves, do not provide T3Leads with your Personally Identifiable Information. You can disable cookies through your Internet browser. However, if you disable Cookies, you may not be able to access or use certain features of this Site or T3Leads` services. T3Leads has no access to or control over third party Cookies technology.

CALIFORNIA DO NOT TRACK DISCLOSURE: Because an industry-standard Do-Not-Track protocol has not yet been established, T3Leads’ information collection practices will continue to operate as described in this Privacy Policy regardless of any “Do Not Track” signals that may be sent by certain browsers or selected by you. However, you may be able to opt-out of being targeted by certain third-party marketers online at www.networkadvertising.org/consumer/opt_out.asp. If you wish to opt-out of receiving communications from T3Leads and/or third-party marketers, you can follow the opt-out instructions in the respective communications that are sent to you.

## Use of Information

Subject to all applicable laws, rules, and regulations, we may use any and all information submitted or collected on this Site to: (a) send you T3Leads updates; (b) share with you related products and services in which you might be interested ("E-mail Offers"); (c) contact you regarding your participation as a Network Member; (d) prevent fraud. We may also use any and all information submitted or collected on this Site for purposes for which you have given your consent, or as may otherwise be permitted by applicable laws, rules, and regulations.

## Sharing of Information

As a general rule, and other than in connection with the limited exceptions set forth below, T3Leads will not sell, share, or rent your Personally Identifiable Information to or with others. Notwithstanding the foregoing, T3Leads may, from time to time, provide information submitted or collected on this Site to certain third-party administrative vendors for various reasons including, without limitation, billing, delivery, and payments. Any and all such third-party vendors are bound by contract to maintain the security and integrity of your Personally Identifiable Information.

T3Leads reserves the right to share information submitted or collected on this Site : (a) where required by law, warrant, subpoena, or legal process; or where requested by a court of competent jurisdiction, governmental authority, or quasi-governmental authority; (b) in the event of T3Leads` bankruptcy, or if T3Leads is sold or acquired; (c) where you are, or are suspected to be, in violation of this Privacy Policy, the T3Leads Terms and Conditions, the T3Leads Advertiser Agreement, and/or the T3Leads Affiliate Agreement; (d) to prevent, address, or remedy fraud, security, or technical issues, which necessarily may include - without limitation - the exchange of such information with trusted third parties for fraud prevention purposes; (e) to improve the design and content of this Site; or, (f) where T3Leads determines such disclosure is necessary to protect the rights of T3Leads or a third party, or to shield T3Leads from liability of any kind.

## Security of Information

T3Leads employs a series of physical and electronic security measures and procedures to safeguard the security and integrity of your personal information from unauthorized access, use, destruction, or disclosure—both online and offline. By way of example and without limiting the generality of the foregoing, T3Leads has managerial security measures in place wherein access to and use of your personal information is limited. As for technical security measures, T3Leads secures data transmission with Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption software, limits access to data storage with password protection, and stores data on secure servers and computers.

Please be advised that, although T3Leads takes all reasonable precautions to protect your data, no data storage or data transmission security is guaranteed. Accordingly, T3Leads cannot, and does not, represent, warrant, or guarantee the complete security of any data storage or data transmission. You agree that your access to and use of this Site and your use of T3Leads` services—which necessarily includes data storage and data transmission—are done at your own risk.

In the event of any known data security breach with respect to your Personally Identifiable Information, T3Leads will notify you and relevant regulatory agencies as may be required by applicable law. Such notice to you may be in the form of e-mail. Please be advised that notice to you may be delayed to address the needs of law enforcement, to determine the scope of the breach, and/or to employ certain remedial measures.

## Access to Personally Identifiable Information

T3Leads retains the submitted or collected on this Site as needed to perform T3Leads` services, to comply with legal obligations, to resolve disputes, and to enforce agreements. If you wish to update or delete your Personally Identifiable Information, you may communicate your desire to do so to T3Leads via certified mail to Office Park IV, 6345 Balboa Blvd., Suite 384, Encino, CA 91316; or via e-mail to [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

## Unsubscribing from E-mail Offers

You may choose to unsubscribe from receipt of E-mail Offers at any time. To do so, you must follow the instruction to unsubscribe at the bottom of any such E-mail Offer or contact T3Leads directly expressing your desire to unsubscribe via certified mail to Office Park IV, 6345 Balboa Blvd., Suite 384, Encino, CA 91316; or via e-mail to [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) All requests to unsubscribe from receipt of such E-Mail Offers from T3Leads are added to T3Leads` Do-Not-Contact list within ten (10) days of receipt. Please be advised you cannot unsubscribe from T3Leads updates, or e-mails regarding your participation as a Network Member.

## Third Party Links

The Site may contain links to third party websites ("Third Party Sites"). Please be advised T3Leads is not responsible for the privacy policies and practices of such Third Party Sites, and this Privacy Policy does not apply to your access to and/or use of such Third Party Websites and/or third party products or services. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by T3Leads. You are encouraged to exercise care when following third party links away from this Site, and to read the privacy policy of any such Third Party Site that collects Personally Identifiable Information. T3Leads is not liable for your access to and use of such Third Party Sites, and your access to and use of such Third Party Sites are done at your own risk.

## Children`s Privacy

This Site is a general audience website and is not specifically designed for or targeted to children. You must be eighteen (18) years of age or older to become a Network Member. T3Leads does not knowingly collect, use, or share any Personally Identifiable Information from children under the age of eighteen (18). If T3Leads becomes aware that Personally Identifiable Information regarding a child under the age of eighteen (18) has been inadvertently collected at this Site, T3Leads will make reasonable efforts to delete it from T3Leads`s records.

## Notification of Changes

T3Leads reserves the right to modify this Privacy Policy or any additional terms that apply to this Site or T3Leads` services. T3Leads will post notice of any such modifications to this Privacy Policy and any additional terms that apply to this Site or T3Leads` services in a clear and conspicuous manner to this Privacy Policy, the T3Leads homepage, and any other place T3Leads may deem appropriate. Any such modifications shall take effect immediately. If you do not agree to any such modified terms, please do not use this Site or T3Leads` services. Your continued use of this Site following notification from T3Leads of any such modifications constitutes your acceptance of any and all such changes in their entirety.

## Headings

The headings for sections contained herein are for convenience only and shall not affect the meaning of the provisions of this Privacy Policy.

## T3Leads` Contact Information

Comments, questions, or concerns about this Privacy Policy or T3Leads` privacy practices may be directed to T3Leads via certified mail to Office Park IV, 6345 Balboa Blvd., Suite 384, Encino, CA 91316; or via email at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)
